Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A young couple standing a crowded room next to a man in military uniform. The female is wearing a short white silk dress with a jacket., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A light haired woman in an elaborate dress, looking off camera., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A group of young children standing on stone steps, one is holding a football., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A family group gathered around a seated bride and groom., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A family group standing around a bride and groom in front some flower arrangements., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- An older female sitting on an armchair with a small child on her lap., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Young females in school uniform, seated around a large wooden table with bookcases in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Women in white coats seated and standing in front of a white stone building., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A family group standing around a large round fountain with the head of a statue on a pedestal., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Three women in western dress standing in front of a low stone wall, female on the left is wearing a plaid skirt., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Two young females in traditional costume., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A large group of young males and females in winter coats with two older females, in the countryside., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Young females in matching outfits with an older couple standing in the middle of them., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A group of school girls in black dresses with white collars in front of a wooden building with large windows., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A group of school children in uniforms standing in front of some buildings., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- School children in black uniforms with white collars and an older woman., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- An older male with a mustache relaxing on a couch in front of a window., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A female in western clothes holding a small cat, standing on a short flight of stairs., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A male reclining on a bed with a cigarette in his hand., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- An older couple standing in front of a house., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- People swimming in an outdoor swimming pool., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A group of six women in western dress, standing in front of a building., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A family group standing in front of a stone wall with the Bosphorous in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A hilly landscape with houses dotting the shoreline with jetties., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Two females in formal dresses dancing with a blurry saxophone in the foreground., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A young couple, female is wearing a light patterned dress with a small bow at the collar., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A young couple on their wedding day surrounded by other couples, with a large mirror in the background. Same bride from AD-MC-007_ref794., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A bride flanked by two females in light dresses. Same bride from AD-MC-007_ref793., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- An older couple in coats, standing in a winter landscape., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Three females sitting on some rocks in the countryside with mountains in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A family group sitting on a bench in front of a grassy hill with a large stone building in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Two females standing in front of stone wall, in dark outfits., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A couple seated at a table with two young children in the backyard of a house., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A couple on their wedding day. The bride is seated on a chair with flowers on her lap. Turkish writing on the front in black ink., 3 August 1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A group of young males and females walking along a stone pathway with a stone arch in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Three young females in the same black dresses with white collars and an older male standing behind them., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A young couple seated on a chair with a young female in betwen them, making a funny face., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A large group couples seated around a table with beer bottles on it., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A young couple on their wedding day, standing on an Oriental carpet with a meander print curtain in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Three females in a military jeep., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A young female seated on a ledge in a light dress with flower details. Turkish writing on the front in blue ink. Studio Can, Izmir., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A group of females in military uniform, with a black stamp of 794., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A group of females in skirt suits, seated on benches with an older male in a suit standing in the back row., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A young female in a tear-shaped print dress, seated in a wooden chair. Foto Park, Izmir., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A group of females seated around a table, the female on the far left is wearing a wedding dress., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Three males in military uniform., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A female in a dark patterned dress flanked by two young males in matching outfits. Studio Alev., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A beared male with a hat on., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A young couple, female in a black dress with a tuxedo front, male in a checkered suit., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A young male, standing in front of a stone wall, wearing a football uniform with cleats., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Three men on a football pitch standing in front of the goal., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Five men in sports kit standing in an empty field, with buildings in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A large group of young children and two older females seated in the middle., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A group of young females seated on the grass in front of a large brick building., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A family group with a bride standing in the middle, in front of an old stone and wooden building. Same bride from AD-MC-007_ref704 and AD-MC-007_ref728., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- An older male in a dark jacket with a short tie and a toothbrush mustache. Turkish writing in blue ink. Foto Isik., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A family group, with an older couple seated in chairs and a young male in military uniform in the back row., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- An older male in a dark suit standing in front of a stone building with a wooden framed window in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- An older male in uniform with a mustache, standing in front of a picket fence and a pickaxe on the ground in front of him., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A family group, mostly wearing sunglasses, standing on a hill top with a body of water in the background., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A family group of older females, gathered in front of a mosaic tiled wall., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Young female in a light patterned dress leaning on a piano, holding a large balloon., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A young male looking off camera in military uniform with Turkish writing in blue ink. Studio Turk., 9 October 1946 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A young couple on their wedding day, Turkish writing in green ink on the front., 12 June 1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A young couple on their wedding day standing on a checkered tile floor., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Two couples seated at a glass table, older male is signing a book with flowers on the table., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A group of mostly males seated at long dinner tables with small glass bottles on them., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A large group of males, in western clothes, some smoking, possibly at the beach., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A young female in a dark dress with checkered bows in her hair sitting on a large stone walkway. Same girl in AD-MC-007_ref862., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A couple, female is wearing a black dress with a flower at the collar, male has a pair of glasses in his breast pocket. Turkish writing in blue ink., 3 May 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Two young females in light flowered dresses with an older female embracing them, in front of plants., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A group of young males in suits, one is reading a newspaper and another is giving bunny ears to another male., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A group of young male military officiers at the beach, with a lighthouse in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Older males in suits in an auditorium., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A young female in a sequined dress shaking hands with a male in a suit. Foto Yalim, Bursa., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Men in uniform, holding horses in a winter landscape., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Young females, mostly veiled, some in matching outfits, seated on a sofa., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A young couple holding hands in front of a large flower arrangement with a radio in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Two young females in short dresses, locking arms, standing in front of a wooden faced counter., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Two females in matching outfits, locking arms with a third female in a dark coat, with flower arrangements in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Two young females, one in a light dress with a dark collar and one in a black dress, standing in front of some curtains., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- A female sitting at a desk talking on a telephone., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- People sitting in an office at desk, with filing cabinets and lots of flowers., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Females of varying ages seated behind a desk with a telephone on it., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Young females in athletic track suits, one is holding a plaque., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- A family group, males and females of varying ages. Two little boys in the foreground are looking off camera., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Five men in military uniform, pulling fishing net out of a boat on the beach., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- A family group surrounding a bride and groom, a little girl with cat eye glasses is standing in front of them., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A family group at the beach. A young male and female standing behind three older people., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A young couple on dancing, female is wearing a light dress with trumpet sleeves., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A family group seated in a living room, older male is wearing a suit with bow tie and one female is wearing a light flower patterned dress., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A family group gathered around a table with a birthday cake with candles on it., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- An older female in a skirt, holding her arms up, with wooden chairs in the background., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Five young females sitting at a table with plates and utencils., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A family group on a road lined by orchards with a car wheel in the foreground., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A young female in a dark dress with checkered bows in her hair with the water in the background. Same female in AD-MC-007_ref835., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A young female in a light turtle neck sweater and dark skirt., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Two young females wearing light colored, patterned dresses, hugging each other., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The Bosphorous coastline., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A young child in furry pants and sweater. Turkish writing in black ink., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A family group gathered under a tree in the country side with a low stone wall in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- An older couple, female in a black dress looking at a man in a suit seated in a wicker chair. Studio Yesim, Aksaray, Istanbul., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Two females in bathing suits, sitting on a white wall with mountains in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Two older females in dark dress in the woods., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- An older male in a dark suit, with a young female sitting on his lap., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A female in a dark skirt suit, holding the hand of a young male in a white outfit, walking., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- a female in a white dress and hat, standing in front of a large tree and some buildings., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A young child in a dark coat with a fur lined collar seated on a square black., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A young girl in a light dress seated one a wooden chair, with a patterend quilt hanging in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A family group gathered around a circular dining table set for dinner., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A group of females of varying ages, with a small table set with food., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A family group in winter coats in the mountains in front of a sign "Seytanin Ayak Izi Dilek Tasi - Devil's stone of wish", undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A young male and young female receiving a diploma/award from two older men on a stage., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A youth in a striped shirt, posing with one hand on hip and one behind the head., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Two males in suits, walking on the street with large buildings in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A young male in a dark suit and a young female in a light jacket, in front of a painted backdrop., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A young female and two older males, one with a knife cutting into a cake., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A female in a light sleeveless dress and short hair with a moutaintop settlement in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A young male and a young female seated on ornate chairs., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A family group seated around a rectangular table with a tall stone wall and trees in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A bride seated in the corner of a room with three females embracing her., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A group of older females in a class room with a chalk board with writing in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A group of young girls in white dresses on a stage with an older couple and flower arrangements., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A family group portrait with the bride and groom seated in the front row and flower arrrangements in the foreground., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A group of young men in military uniform gathered on the street in front of some stone buildings., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A bride in a dress and veil, standing with a female in front of some wooden chairs and a stone wall., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A young girl in a dress and jacket, standing in a park., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A family group sitting behind a circular table with a large palm in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A mixed group of males and females in winter coats standing in front of a columned building., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- An older male standing in his underwear in front of a door., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A family group standing in a garden., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A male and two older females standing on the side of a road with a horse drawn wagon approaching them., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A bridge with a large updo sitting in a chair with an older woman holding her and a young child in the foreground., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A woman in a white dress holding a baby., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A group of school childern, standing in front of a building with a sign on it, "Namazgah Ilkokulu"., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A large group of young males in suits. A male in the middle right is wearing a white hat on his head., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A group of young females in the same uniform and young males in suits, with buildings in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Young females in the same black dress with white collar, standing in front of a wood building with white bars on the windows., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young couple on their wedding day, standing on a flower patterned carpet with sheer curtains in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young male in military uniform with an anchor on his hat., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- An older female and a younger male sitting on a coach with a lamp behind them., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young male standing in front of a doorway wearing a white shirt and shorts., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A group of five young children, one male wearing a fez and holding a walking stick and one female with an umbrella and a fan., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young male in a white outfit with a patterned cape, holding a bowl with flames in it., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young male wearing a white shirt with a sash and hat, under a flower patterned blanket., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- An older couple looking off camera to the left, female is wearing a houndstooth jacket., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young woman in a patterned skirt suit. Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A group of young males in military uniform, taken from ground level., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of couples in formal attire with ballons overhead., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of males of varying ages in military uniform holding rifles., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A mixed group of school children at desks., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A bride and groom on the wedding day with some guests, flower arrangements in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of school aged children in uniform standing in front of old stone buildings., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A bride with flowers in her hands, standing with two males in suits, one with a tie and one with a bowtie., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A bride and groom, bride is holding a bouquet of flowers with two large flower arrangements on the floor in front., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A bride on her wedding day with two women hugging her., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of men sitting at square tables, some in military dress whites., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A profile of a young female in a white dress, with a small necklace on and a shoulder length hair cut., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A bride and groom on their wedding day, standing with another couple in front of an old wooden building and a stone wall., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A large group of males and females at a large banquet table in a room with wood columns., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Five women in western clothes behind the desk in an office., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A male in a dark vest holding a baby in a sweater., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Two older females, one in a black jacket and one in a patterened turtleneck. Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A young couple on the deck of a boat with water and some buildings behind them., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A family group in the countryside, next to a river. Turkish writing in blue ink., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A young couple, male is wearing what looks like a Boy Scout uniform, female is wearing a pinstripped jacket., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A young man standing with his hands on his hips on a tree lined street with some houses in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Three young males in white outfits behind a desk with a leather bag on it., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A group of males dressed in military uniform lined up for inspection., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A group of males in military uniform in the sand., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A large group of males in military uniform, with hoops on their caps., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Three males in military uniform and a fourth wearing a fez. Foto Ankara, Kütahya, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A group of young males in sports uniform on a dirt football pitch. One male is holding a football., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A group of males in white shirts and shorts and some in winter clothes. A seated male is holding a dog., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A young child in winter clothes, standing in the snow outside a stone building., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A bride and groom seated around a table, with some guests with flowers on it., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- An older male with two younger males and a small barking dog in front of a place and flowers., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A young girl in a black and gold traditional outfit with red curtains in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- An older female in a dress feeding a man reclining in the grass next to trees., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Two males in military uniform with a young boy sitting in a car., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- A male in a military hat and winter coat, holding a leather bag and gloves in a winter landscape., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Males in military uniform sitting at a table eating and drinking., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Children in school uniform and their teachers standing on the stairs of a building., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- A couple and their son at the beach in bathing suits., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Males in military uniform seated in couches around a round wooden table with an ashtray on it., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Two men with toothbrush mustaches seated behind a small wooden table with a large piece of machinery behind them., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- A couple, female in a light top with a small flower at the top button, male is wearing a light suit with a tie. Foto Uslu., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Four females of varying ages seated around a dinner table laided with food and bottles., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A young male in a white short suit, with a sash and hat. Studio Ideal., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Two males and one female in bathing suits sitting at the beach., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Two males next to an older female in a flower dress seated in a chair., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Two young males in western dress, standing in front of a photographic backdrop of a river scene., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A young female in a light dress with a large flower at the breast, having adjustments made by an older covered woman., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Men in military hats and long winter coats standing in front of a train car., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A bride with a large veil with two females and a male in a double breasted suit. Foto Yalim, Bursa, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Four females in white lab coats sitting on a bench next to a fountain surrounded by plants., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A couple and two young males in matching outfits of white shirts with sashes and hat, sitting with books on their laps., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A young child with a white sweat suit and a shirt with snowflakes on it, next to an inflatable duck. Turkish writing on the front in blue ink., 1 May 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A shirtless male, flexing with some mountains in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Four females seated a table with food and cake on it., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A family group gathered around a table with a large birthday cake with candles in the middle., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- An older female in a dress, with two younger females in pants, standing on a balcony with buildings in the background., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A male and a female on the dance floor, female is sitting in a shiny skirt and short top with blonde hair., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Two males in suits, one with a mustache and a female in a black outfit with a large white collar and a updo. Foto Güzel., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Two young females, one in pants and a light striped top., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)